ADRIAN VALDEPEÑAS

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

www.avaldepenas.dev



in/adrianvaldepenas/



valdepenas.adrian@gmail.com



0998-856-0686

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, and Javascript
- ReactJS, NodeJS, and Redux
- · SASS, Bootstrap, Ant Design, and Styled Components
- Express, Sitecore and WordPress
- SQL and MongoDB
- Root-cause analysis, teamwork, and communication, ability to work under pressure. adaptability

PROFILE

As a frontend web developer with 3 years of experience, I have specialized in ReactJS and have a deep understanding of the library's core concepts and best practices. I have developed complex, responsive web applications using ReactJS, and am experienced in using libraries such as Redux, SASS, Ant Design and Styled Components.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Zuitt Coding Bootcamp

JAN 2020 - MAY 2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Technological Institute of the **Philippines**

JUN 2010 - MAR 2015

EXPERIENCE

APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

Accenture Inc.

APR 2022 - Present

- Developed, updated, and managed templates for the Sitecore CMS.
- Provided assistance with configuring Google Analytics on clients' websites.
- Translated designs from Zeplin into code using ReactJS, SASS, and other relevant libraries.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Sqreem Technologies Inc.

SEP 2020 - MAR 2022

- Worked in collaboration with multiple teams to implement a React version of pre-existing applications.
- Ensure the upkeep and modifications of in-house web application tools developed using pure JavaScript.
- Developed React components utilizing Sass, Ant Design, and Redux Toolkit.

INTERESTS







